{
    "subject": "resource/The_Towering_Inferno",
    "predicate": "ontology/director",
    "object": "resource/John_Guillermin",
    "human_readable": "The director of The Towering Inferno is John Guillermin.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9458853602409363,
            "question": "Besides The Towering Inferno, what other films has John Guillermin directed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8956172466278076,
            "question": "Who directed the movie The Towering Inferno?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8615190982818604,
            "question": "What is the name of the director of The Towering Inferno?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7261307239532471,
            "question": "Name a film directed by John Guillermin."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5289329886436462,
            "question": "Is The Towering Inferno considered a classic film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5055790543556213,
            "question": "What genre is The Towering Inferno?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4842280447483063,
            "question": "What awards has John Guillermin won for his directing?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.42710983753204346,
            "question": "Is John Guillermin known for directing disaster films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.39507386088371277,
            "question": "What year was The Towering Inferno released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.27874910831451416,
            "question": "What are some common themes in John Guillermin's films?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The director of The Towering Inferno is John Guillermin.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4107_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What year was The Towering Inferno released?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4107_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is John Guillermin known for directing disaster films?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4107_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What awards has John Guillermin won for his directing?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4107_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4107_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4107_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4107_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4107_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4107_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4107_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4107_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4107_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4107_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4107_98.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here's the structured JSON response:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nAll 7 documents provide information about John Guillermin, and each document mentions that he was a director who worked on the film \"The Towering Inferno\". Therefore, this statement is supported by the provided context."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents repeatedly mention that John Guillermin directed \"The Towering Inferno\" and the 1976 \"King Kong,\" which supports the statement that the director of \"The Towering Inferno\" is John Guillermin."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}